The next keyword we will look at is used when
we are just looking to get a small sample
of what is in a table or tables that
have been joined. I have a query that
shows people and their addresses. When I
execute this, we see that the query produces
almost 19000 records. The query ran quickly here,
but if you notice that a query is doing so many
things that it's running slowly, and you are just
testing a query, you can limit this to show a top
number of records. To make this happen, I will add
the keyword TOP after the word SELECT and then a
number, 100 in this case. The top 100 records
will return as soon as I execute this statement.
Should you decide you want this sorted a certain
way, as we saw elsewhere in this course, you would
need to add an ORDER BY clause to the end of the
query, as I will do here to sort this PostalCode,
and then I will execute this again. Now, we
see the top 100 records sorted by postal code.